The Devil Below is a horror, thriller film directed by Bradley Parker.
A group of four amateur adventurers who specialize in exploring remote and forsaken places pay a visit to Shookum Hills, a
town in the remote Appalachian Mountains which was abandoned decades ago due to a mysterious coal mine fire.
Arianne, played by Alicia Sanz.
Darren, played by Adan Canto.
Schuttmann, played by Will Patton.
Jaime, played by Zach Avery.
Shawn, played by Chinaza Uche.
Terry, played by Jonathan Sadowski.
The Devil Below is a 2021 American horror film directed by Bradley Parker.
The film stars Alicia Sanz, Adan Canto, Zach Avery, Chinaza Uche,
Jonathan Sadowski, Jesse LaTourette and Will Patton.
It was released on March 5, 2021, by Vertical Entertainment.
The tone is dark and intense.